Chadwick Swenson

ChadwickSwenson.com / ChadSwenson@gmail.com / 510.384.8049

Overview

Currently designing Yahoo Fantasy Sports mobile iOS and Android.

Selected to be a member of 10 recent grads in Marissa Mayer's Design Associates Program.

Worked on next gen iOS messenger app at Yahoo.

Designed mobile app at Adherial with more than one million in revenue in less than one year of launch.

Skills

Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch, animation, prototyping, pixate, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Swift

Education

Oregon State University

Bachelors of Science

Computer Science; minor in

Business

Employment

Designer at Yahoo

Jan 2014 - Present in Sunnyvale CA

Worked on next gen messenger app for iOS. Currently designing Yahoo Fantasy Sports for both Android and iOS. Visual design, interaction design, and prototyping primarily on mobile.

Product Designer at Adherial (mobile app startup) March 2013 - December 2014 in Portland OR and SF CA

Work with team of five software engineers, one HCl researcher, and three founders. Build prototypes. Function as an evangelist for user experience and product strategy. Designed iOS, Android, and desktop web apps.

Freelance Product Designer

Sep 2009 - May 2013

Prototyping, wireframes, Photoshop, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL.

Software Development Intern at Intel

Mar 2012 - Sep 2012

Developed and designed application for storing, searching, exporting, and comparing hardware data.

Full Stack Developer at Connected Studios

Jun 2010 - Mar 2012 in Marin CA

Children's flash game startup. Wrote Java on the backend and Flash, HTML, CSS and JavaScript on the front.